Text:1.a floodplain farmer 2.a popular local figure who was well regarded for his leadership in civic groups3.lacked experience in dealing with the Kronosian government 4.(First Step) take the statistics assembled by the Elodis Community Health Center to the Abila office of the Minister of Interior, but was met with skepticism.5. August 18 1998 ten-year old Juliana Vann, daughter of Lemual and Neske Vann, died of leukemia associated with benzene toxicity. This event also brought (the first serious schism) in the POK. an iconic image of Juliana smiling down over a daisy, tinted in Warhol-esque colors. It was then that public awareness for POK across Kronos began rising.