1.HB’s lifelong friend2.used his business experience to form relationships with the Kronosian government and outside agencies3.proposed to the activists that they form a social movement organization with an identity brand---POK4.contacted Wellness for All (WFA), (First increasement in members: who confirmed the presence of contaminants consistent with pollution from Hyper Acidic Substrate Removal, a gas drilling technique employed by GAStech at the Tiskele Bend fields. The WFA published these test results in several international journals, which gathered attention in the media and brought new members to the POK. )5.(First dealing with GAStech: HB and Osvaldo sought to meet with GAStech to discuss the contamination issue with results of WFA testing, and after much persistence, were able to meet with Hank Fluss, GAStech’s Chief Operating Officer.  Fluss assured the men that he would discuss the contamination issue with GAStech CEO Sten Sanjorge, Jr., but there is no evidence that Sanjorge made any changes to his company’s operations at the Tiskele Bend fields.)6.(First and the only support from goverment)HB and Osvaldo attended several meetings with the Minister of Health, Cesare Nespolathe --- only government official who was willing to engage with them. In July 1999 he sponsored a bill to create an additional tax on oil and gas development. The tax measure was defeated in March 2001, and Nespola died suddenly(Why? Murdered?) in June 2001 . Nespola’s successor, Vincent Kapelou, the 28-year-old nephew of President Kapelou,(May hint the relationship between GAStech and the government) was less sympathetic to the POK’s plight and refused to re-introduce the tax measure to the General Assembly.7.POK turned to protesting at the entrance to the government-controlled Tiskele Bend fields in August 2001 in order to refocus attention on their cause. (the first time POK supporters were arrested)（the first of many POK public protests）