1.was the leader and co-founder of a small environmental activist group, Save Our Wildlands, which formed at the University of Abila. She joined the POK in 2005.  2.believes in persistent, peaceful protest3.2009.6.21，take over Elian Karel as the leader of POK.4.2009.10.19 POK members are arrested. POK radicialization caused due to Silvia Marek’s weak ability to some extend.5.2012.4 and 2014.11, Silvia Marek appealed to the citizens of Kronos to join her for peaceful protest, in support of  increased government accountability.