1.the older brother of Juliana Vann, the 10-year-old girl who died in 1998 after an illness related to drinking contaminated water from the Tiskele River, and nephew to Mandor Vann.  2.advocate for a more forceful approach to gaining attention to the plight of people living downstream of Tiskele Bend. (may be the suspect) 3.has been arrested several times for civil disobedience and trespassing during POK rallies.